(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T13:54:26.166632",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
骨を並べては みんなほらライアー
Lining up bones, you're all liars, see?
理屈だなんてゴミ箱は 身に覚えあるんでしょ アンサー
As for trash like excuses, you know it all too well, right? That's your answer.
チク チク 痛いのね
It hurts with a prickling pain, doesn't it?
エゴイズムに踊らされて 巻き込まれてく アンレ アンレ
Swept up in egoism, getting dragged into it, unles, unles!
焼き付けて あくまでも 癒やしで当てましょう
Branding it on—no matter what, let's soothe it away with healing.
ディンドン ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong!
響かせディンドン 笑い声 はは
Ringing out ding-dong, laughter—haha!
と叫べ
Shout it out!
ディンドンディンドン 鳴らしたよディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ring it out, ding-dong!
破るのが先か 破るのが先か
Will you tear it off first, or will you break first?
噛みつきやしないわ
I won't bite you, you know.
慰めもしないわ
I won't comfort you either.
私のものね
You're mine, aren't you?
飽きたらのディスタンス
Once you're sick of it, no distance!
闇にまぎれて甘いチョコレート溶かして
Melting sweet chocolate hidden in the dark,
くるみざみたくさん繋げて 剥ぎ取っていく
Tangled up and tightly bound, and stripped away step by step,
鍵の姿化けて瞳を貸していく
Disguising as a key and lending my eyes,
ぴりつが痛むのね
It hurts sharply, doesn't it?
メカニズムに踊らされて 巻き込まれてく アンレ アンレ
Swept up in the mechanism, getting dragged into it, unles, unles!
間違えても正しくても
Whether you're wrong or right,
癒やして当てましょう まだダメですか？
Let's soothe it away—is it still not enough?
ディンドン ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong!
狂わせディンドン 最後に はは と叫べ
Driving you crazy, ding-dong, finally shouting "Haha!"
ディンドン ディンドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong!
君好みアーカイブ 惨敗もマージン
The archives you like, a margin of utter defeat,
後悔しないの 君に近付いた
without regrets, I drew closer to you
昨日の飾りを 引き千切って
and tore off yesterday's decorations.
さあ どうぞ お好きなの ear ear ear
Come, do as you like, with these ears, ears, ears!
煩い通りは 少し苦手なの
I'm a little weak at bustling streets,
繁華街の目を光らせる
my eyes glimmering in the shopping district.
監視体制も ラクなもんじゃないね
Surveillance isn't an easy thing either,
迂闊に昼寝も 出来ないくらいに
not even being able to take a siesta.
小娘一人は 傘一本
The lone young girl carries a single umbrella,
爪を汚さずに 高みの見物
a spectator without sullying her claws.
被った仮名は 私の真似？
Is that mask she wore an imitation of me?
笑い飛ばしちゃうね
Don't make me laugh!
アタマから手をとけて
Take your hands off my head,
手をとけて
take them off,
撫でたりしないで
don't pet me.
あなたが アタマだけじゃなくなっちゃうの
You won't just be on my mind anymore—
もう耐られない
I can't stand it!
ヘッドホンは 外さない方が
Maybe it'd be better if
いいんじゃないの？
you don't take your headphones off?
君の攻略本 私のコレクション
Your strategy guides are my collection,
色形サイズ 全て取り揃えています
assembled by color, shape, and size.
二週間前は 可愛い赤色
Two weeks ago, it was a cute red;
三日前は 確かなクールな青色
three days ago, a certain cool blue.
今日の新作は 強気な紫
Today's new work is a confident purple;
明日は君のその隣の邪魔な娘
tomorrow, it's that troublesome girl by your side.
恋の敵のシルエット
The silhouette of a love rival
重なる夜まで あと何時間
piles up in the remaining hours of the night.
泥棒猫はどっちなのだろう？
Just which of us is the homewrecker?
アタマから手をとけて
Take your hands off my head,
手をとけて
take them off,
撫でたりしないで
don't pet me.
あなたが アタマだけじゃなくなっちゃう前に
Before you become more than just a thought—
やめてよ
stop it!
目を開けて！ 目を開けて！
Open your eyes! Open your eyes!
ちゃんとアタシを見て
Look at me properly!
あなたが「アタシだけ」じゃなくなっちゃうの
I can't bear you being about anyone else—
もう耐られない
I can't stand it!
離れての馬鹿馬鹿しい
How foolish to be apart,
一人じゃ辛いから
because being alone is painful.
お願い
Please—
「もう、そっちがその気なら？」
"Well, if that's how you feel,"
晩餐会とかふぁっと尻尾で凍え気味にしちゃっていいですか？
"can I freeze you with a flick of my tail?"
一人じゃ傷付かない
I won't get hurt alone,
「あ、そうですか。じゃあ もうあなたなんか知らない！」
"Ah, is that so? Then I don't care about you anymore!"
もう手をとけて 手をとけて
Take your hands off my head, take them off,
撫でたりしないで
don't pet me.
あなたが アタマだけじゃなくなっちゃう前に
Before you become more than just a thought—
やめてよ
stop it!
目を開けて！ 目を開けて！
Open your eyes! Open your eyes!
ちゃんとアタシを見て
Look at me properly!
あなたが 誰かと楽しそうにしてるの
Seeing you having fun with someone else—
なんか勘違いしちゃうよ
it makes me misunderstand things!
撫でて欲しいの
I want you to pet me.
あなたが アタマだけじゃなくなっちゃうの もう耐られない
I can't stand you not being mine alone anymore!
はーいということで みんな今日はつけてくれてありがとう！
Hii! So everyone, thank you so much for celebrating today with me!
いや今回のちょこのお誕生日ライブは なんと や、このねサムネにも書いてあるんですけど
And you know, for Choco's birthday live this time... it's actually written right there on the thumbnail, but
ちょこ先生はてぇてぇに囲まれたい 柚子ちょこ生誕祭2023ということで
"Choco-sensei wants to be surrounded by teetee" - Yuzuki Choco's Birthday Festival 2023!
なんとかね いやもうゲストもうサムネでバレちゃってるんですけど
And well, the guests are already kind of spoiled on the thumbnail,
まあどういう組み合わせなのかはね まあちょこの推しメンということでお楽しみにしててください！
but please look forward to seeing what kind of combinations we have in store!
そしてそして今回の配信のハッシュタグこちら こちら！
And then, the hashtag for today's stream is right here, right here!
チャープ 柚子ちょこ生誕祭2023で 2023で、あっ2023で呟いてください お願いします！
"#YuzukiChocoBirthday2023" - please tweet with 2023! I'm counting on you!
そっか
I see.
ゲストパートの方に映っていきましょう！呼んできまーす！
Let's move on to the guest part! I'll call them out!
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
ディスコ ココ
Disco, here
計算する女の子
A calculating girl,
期待してる男の子
a boy with his hopes up,
ときめいてる女の子
a girl whose heart is fluttering,
気にしないふり男の子
a boy pretending he doesn't care.
バレンタインが近づいて デパートの地下も揺れる
Valentine's is getting closer, shaking up the department store basement too.
計算する女の子
A calculating girl,
期待してる男の子
a boy with his hopes up,
お願い想いが届くようにね
Please, I hope my feelings reach you,
とっても心込めた甘いの
putting all my heart into something sweet.
お願い想いが届くといいな
Please, I really hope my feelings get through,
対決の日が来た
the day of the showdown is here.
お願い想いが届くようにね
Please, I hope my feelings reach you,
とっても心込めた甘いの
putting all my heart into something sweet.
お願い想いが届くといいな
Please, I really hope my feelings get through,
対決の日が来た
the day of the showdown is here.
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
ディスコ ココ
Disco, here
計算する女の子
A calculating girl,
期待してる男の子
a boy with his hopes up,
ときめいてる女の子
a girl whose heart is fluttering,
気にしないふり男の子
a boy pretending he doesn't care.
バレンタインが近づいて デパートの地下も揺れる
Valentine's is getting closer, shaking up the department store basement too.
計算する女の子
A calculating girl,
期待してる男の子
a boy with his hopes up,
お願い想いが届くようにね
Please, I hope my feelings reach you,
とっても心込めた甘いの
putting all my heart into something sweet.
なぜか教室がダンスフロアに
For some reason, the classroom's a dance floor.
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
ディスコ ココ
Disco, here
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
ディスコ ココ
Disco, here
チョコレート・ディスコ
Chocolate disco
はーい！ということで
Hii! So,
イェーイ！フーフー！イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Woo! Yeah! Yeah!
いやでもこのステージね
Man, this stage though,
そう。ねえ、うたたんのステージ借りちゃいました！
Yeah. We borrowed Utatan's stage!
ありがとうございまーす！イェーイ！
Thank you so much! Yay!
めっちゃありがとー！
Thank you so much!
イェーイ！というわけで
Yay! So,
我々トップバッター？
Are we the top batters?
そうです！
That's right!
トップバッターらしいぞ！
We're the top batters!
てえてえ始まりだ！第1弾トップバッターは
What a heartwarming start! The first top batter is...
CCWataコンビだ！イェーイ！
The CCWata duo! Yay!
挟まれてさ...お尻で挟まれて物理的に挟まれてたんだけど
We were squeezed... squeezed between them, physically sandwiched between them,
え！？お尻で挟まれて？
Huh!? Sandwiched by butts?
もなんかお聞きことあったりする？
Do you have anything you want to ask?
あー
Ah...
やっぱ獅子わたと言えば
Speaking of Shishiwata,
やっぱりボタン様がわため様を やばパクってよしたいみたいなね
as expected, Botan-sama wants to "nom" Watame-sama, right?
いつも食べる時ってさ いい感じじゃないですか、これね。
Whenever you eat, you know, it's a good vibe, right?
いつも召し上がる時って どういう食べ方をされてるんですか？
When you usually eat, how do you eat it?
えっとね、最近目の前でキープ
Umm, lately, keeping it right in front of your eyes—
それ自分の目の前でキープしますか？
Do you keep it right in front of your eyes?
自分の目の前にして言うのあれなんですけどね
I shouldn't say this right in front of me, but
最近ちょっとおすすめの食べ方がありまして
lately I have a recommended way of eating.
お、ラムしゃぶです。
Oh, lamb shabu.
ラムしゃぶ！
Lamb shabu!
ラムしゃぶです！
次ラムしゃぶか。
Next is lamb shabu, huh.
最近まではね、焼くとかさ、しゃぶしゃぶーとかだったと思うんですけど、最近のブームはね、ラムしゃぶなんです。
Until recently, I think it was grilling or shabu-shabu, but the recent boom is lamb shabu.
なるほどね。
I see.
美味しい食べ方があるんだね。
There's a delicious way to eat it, huh.
でもね、色々味変もできるしね。
But you can also change up the flavors in various ways.
なるほどね。
I see.
じゃ、チョコ先生も良かったら今度からラムしゃぶをね、こうやって、あーってやってくれたら
Well, Choco-sensei, if you'd like, from now on, with lamb shabu, you do like this, "ah"—
いやー、いいですか？食べちゃっていいですか？強奪しちゃって
Man, is it okay? Can I just eat it? Can I snatch it away?
まあ、今日は生誕だからさ、一か、一かじりぐらいね。
Well, since it's a birthday today, about one bite.
あ、じゃあ真ん中に来てもらって、プレゼント、え？
Ah, then come to the center, a present, eh?
なんでなんで？真ん中に来てもらって、主役だから。
Why why? Come to the center, because you're the main character.
だって今私がプレゼントって言おうとして、言ってたじゃん。
Because I was just about to say "present", you were saying it!
だったらね、プレゼントは真ん中に来るんだよ。
If so, presents come to the center, you know.
プレゼントだぞ。
It's a present!
はい。
Yes.
じゃあハッピーステーリーやっとくぜ。
Then I'll do Happy Birthday.
ハッピーバースデートゥーユー！
Happy Birthday to you!
プレゼントです！
It's a present!
いただきます！
Itadakimasu!
いいですか？
Is it good?
怖いよ。
Scary!
やっぱりね、数奇な運命だったんだよ、君は。
As expected, it was a strange fate for you, huh.
サイコパスじゃん。
You're a psychopath.
いや、ボタン様と一緒に食べちゃいましょう。
No, let's eat together with Botan-sama.
食べちゃいましょう。
Let's eat it.
いやだいやだ！今合宿所のタイムだよ、みんな！
No no! This is training camp time, everyone!
みんな集合だ！
Everyone gather around!
カメラ目線決めていく。
We'll nail the camera angles.
えっへへ！
Hehehe!
ノルトの！
Nolt's—!
ノルトのカメラ目線！何が何だか。
Nolt's camera angle! What is what.
まあね、これからもっとてぇてぇコンビがね、見れるから楽しみにしておこうぜ。
Well, let's look forward to seeing even more teetee duos from now on.
ね、見てよ、見てよ。
Right, look at it, look at it.
はい、とりあえずね、頑張って。
Okay, for now, do your best.
お腹いっぱいになりました。ありがとうございました。
I'm full. Thank you very much.
頑張ったね！
You worked hard!
この後も盛り上がりますからね！ありがとうございます！
It'll get even more exciting after this! Thank you!
バイバ～イ！はーいということで、お次はどなたかなー？
Bye-bye! So, who is up next?
どうぞー！
Go ahead!
らん らん らん ～
La la la...
わん、つー、すりー
One, two, three,
奇怪なステップで踊り出すbeat
dancing out to a bizarre step beat.
今宵輝くネオンの下で光る私
Me shining under tonight's neon lights.
可愛い kawaii 召し使い達
Cute kawaii servants,
あの子はどこに？
where is that child?
うだうだごろごろだらだらニャンニャン何もしたくない！
Moaning, lolling, dawdling, meowing, I don't want to do anything!
甘い甘いチョコが食べたいの
I want to eat sweet, sweet chocolate.
アツイ アツイ ラテが飲みたい
I want to drink hot, hot latte.
ホクホクのお肉食べたいの
I want to eat fluffy, steaming meat.
トロットロのチーズが食べたい
I want to eat gooey, melting cheese.
フカフカのベッドで寝たい
I want to sleep in a fluffy bed.
うとうと おやすみなさい zzz
Dozing off, good night zzz.
わがまま らん らん らん　誰も逆らわないで
Selfish la la la, nobody go against me,
ワタシ かわいいでしょ？　おお願い give give me！
Aren't I cute? Please give give me!
何でもすべて甘い続けて
Spoil me with everything continuously,
何もかも許される　だって私が一番可愛いんだから
because everything is forgiven, since I'm the cutest of all.
すいーつは 香ばしい匂いで騒ぎ出す鼓動
Sweets—a heartbeat stirred up by a savory scent.
今宵 月明かりの下で 誰を◯る？
Whom am I to [maru] under tonight's moonlight?
ギロチン 、 銃殺 、 火あぶり 、 切腹　お好きな オプション で
Guillotine, firing squad, burning at the stake, seppuku—with your favorite option,
誰も私には敵わない
nobody is a match for me.
つ 、 ま 、 ら 、 な 、 い
How bo-ri-ng.
苦い苦い肝が食べたい
I want to eat bitter, bitter liver.
紅い紅いスープ飲みたい
I want to drink crimson, crimson soup.
ホクホクお肉食べたいの
I want to eat steaming meat.
甘い甘いそれじゃ足りない
Sweet, sweet—that's not enough.
歪んだ face もっと見せて？
Show me that distorted face more?
らん らん らん らん らん らん らん らん
La la la la la la la la...
ほら 、 まだまだ 足りないわ
Look, it's still not enough.
わがままな 私のこと 愛して くれる 誰か を 待っている の
Waiting for someone who will love my selfish self.
孤独な夜に一人枕濡らして 秒針を眺めているの だって私が ね？
Wetting my pillow alone on a lonely night, looking at the second hand, because I... right?
世界で一番おひめさま
I'm the number one princess in the world
そう言う扱い心得てよね
So make sure you know how to treat me
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気付くこと
First, notice when I have a different hairstyle
その二 ちゃんときまで見ること いいね?
Second, make sure you look closely at my shoes, ok?
その三 私の一言には 三つの言葉で返事すること
Third, for every word I say, reply with three words
わかったら 右手が お留守なのを 何とかして!
If you understand, do something about my empty right hand!
別にわがままなんて 言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish
キミに心から思って欲しいの かわいいって
I want you to truly feel from your heart that I'm cute
世界で一番おひめさま
Number one princess in the world
気が付いて ねぇねぇ
Notice me, hey, hey
待たせるなんて論外よ
Making me wait is out of the question
ワタシを誰だと思ってるの?
Who do you think I am?
もう何だか 甘いものが食べたい! いますぐに
And now I want something sweet to eat right now!
あー、という ことでね!
Ah, so anyway!
こんばんはー!
Good evening!
ちょっと、今日、可愛い!
Man, today we're so cute!
役ならお前、置いていくからな!
As for the role, I'll leave you behind!
いや今回ね、ちょこはてーてーに挟まれたということで!
So this time, Choco was sandwiched between some preciousness!
ちょっとね、ちょこの推しメン2人に来てもらいましたということで!
We invited Choco's top two favorite members!
推しメンなんてそんなちょこ先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます!
Favorite members? Choco-senpai, happy birthday!
あのー、ちょこあの、お誕生日なんで、あのー今日はわがまま言ってもいいですか?
Um, since it's Choco's birthday, can I be a bit selfish today?
しょうがないな、わがまま姫なんだから!
Can't be helped, since you're the selfish princess!
え、何ですか、わがままっていうのは?
Eh, what do you mean by being selfish?
ちょこ、あの、みこちがはーちゃまに、困らされているところが 見たくて...
Choco, I wanted to see Miko being troubled by Haachama...
待って! とりあえず、豚切られるの?
Wait! Is this getting abruptly cut off?
とりあえずみこ様は、サムネと同じポーズしてもらってもいいですか?
Anyway Miko-sama, could you do the same pose as the thumbnail?
は、はい! わ、分かりました!
O-ok! Understood!
やだー！なんでだよおかしだろこっちから...
No way! Why is this weird, from this side...
あじゃあ、私がこうやってるんで、はーちゃま好きなふりして蹴飛ばすでもなんでもして...
Ah then, since I'm doing this, Haachama, just pretend to kick me or whatever...
やめろや！
Stop it!
これが見たかったの、ちょこ!
This is what I wanted to see, Choco!
ぶり、らぶらぶとかじゃないんだね!
It's not all lovey-dovey and cutesy!
あれ、思ってたのと違うな... ラブラブとかじゃないんだね!
Huh, that's different from what I expected... It's not lovey-dovey at all!
ここはなんか、振り回されるのがいいのかなって。
I guess getting pushed around here is good.
金髪のね、2人に囲まれたらみこもなかなか...
Being surrounded by two blondes, Miko is quite...
じゃあ、止めてって言っていただいて、みこ様は。
Then Miko-sama, tell us to stop.
いいんですか? さっき1発殴るなら誰でもいいんか?
Is that okay? Anyone can punch you once?
いやいやでもね、ちょこ先生、この後もね、ゲストがまだまだいるんですよね!
No no, but Choco-senpai, there are still more guests coming up after this!
はーい! じゃあ最後にちょこ先生、この後も頑張ってと言ってもらっていいですか?
Yay! So finally, Choco-senpai, can you say you love it and work hard after this too?
おおー！ 大好きまーす！ ちょこ先生！ この後もがんばってー！
Ooh! We love you! Choco-senpai! Good luck after this too!
女子校戦争
[Title: Girls' School War]
チャイムのベルぎりぎりで
With a final bell ringing for final exams,
ノーメイク別人の顔で
With a no-makeup, alter-ego face...
すいませすいませすいませんね 眠たおもい
Sorry, sorry, excuse me, sleepy-eyed.
教科書の端に書いた
Written on the margin of a textbook,
屋上に潜む魔物
A monster lurking on the rooftop.
すいませすいませ吸い込まれる 片想い
Sorry, sorry, unrequited love is swallowed up.
3限過ぎれば だいたいみんな本気を出してガチメーク
Once period 3 passes, everyone gets dead serious, full effort.
ジャージがスカートから覗く そこはもう狂地
Peeking from a garter skirt, that's already madness.
女子校戦争 鳴り止まない
Girls' school warfare, the ringing never stops,
美しい花園なんかじゃない
This isn't just some pretty garden.
みんな獲物を狙っている
Everyone's targeting their prey,
テリトリー邪魔させない
Don't let territory get in the way.
女子校戦争 負けられない
Girls' school warfare, you can't lose,
あのイケメン講師を落としたい
I want to make that handsome instructor fall for me.
制服のリボンほほどいたら カウントダウン始まるわ
If the uniform ribbon is undone, the countdown begins.
期末テストぎりぎりで
With a final bell ringing for term tests,
意味なく手を上げアピール
Meaninglessly raising my hand to appeal.
すいませすいませすいませんね 上目遣い
Sorry, sorry, excuse me, looking up with puppy eyes.
教室の隅に寄せた
Tucked away in the corner of the classroom,
補習に潜む魔物
A monster lurking in remedial classes.
すいませすいませ吸い込まれる 子供扱い
Sorry, sorry, being treated like a child, swallowed up.
生物 数学 どうでもいいの 本気をだして即メール
Biology, math, whatever, showing real effort, instant emailing.
マジだる 仮病使い 呼び出す保健室 そこはもう窮地
Serious pseudo-illness, calling out the nurse's office, that's already a tight spot.
女子校戦争 鳴り止まない
Girls' school warfare, the ringing never stops,
麗しい花園なんかじゃない
This isn't just some pretty garden.
みんな火花を散らしている
Everyone's scattering sparks,
抜け駆けは許されない
Escaping is not allowed.
女子校戦争 負けられない
Girls' school warfare, you can't lose,
あの気取った女子を落としたい
I want to make that stuck-up senior fall for me.
制服のフォーク外したなら カウントダウン始まるわ
If the uniform's folk is removed, the countdown begins.
ねえ 先生 教えて
Hey, teacher, tell me,
方程式が解けないの
I can't solve this equation.
ねえ 先生 助けて
Hey, teacher, help me,
あたし 熱があるみたい
It feels like I have a fever.
女子校戦争 鳴り止まない
Girls' school warfare, the ringing never stops,
美しい花園なんかじゃない
This isn't just some pretty garden.
みんな獲物を狙っている
Everyone's targeting their prey,
テリトリー邪魔させない
Don't let territory get in the way.
女子校戦争 負けられない
Girls' school warfare, you can't lose,
あのイケメン講師を落としたい
I want to make that handsome instructor fall for me.
制服の裾めくったら 子供を疎外させないわ
If you peek past the uniform hem, you can't let kids be excluded.
女子校せー
Girls' school...
じゃあね 今日はね
Well, hey, today...
何回何回何回なんだ 寝るんだよ！
You have to go to sleep!
ちょっとプレゼントをあげますか！あげる！プレゼント！
I'll give you a present! Give me a present!
どこだって どんなものになってほしいなら！
Wherever, whatever you want it to be!
えっ、ちょっと待って！
Ah, wait, wait, wait!
やめてっ！
Stop it!
嘘でしょ！？
No way?!
え、待って待って待って、全然違うじゃん！
Huh, wait, wait, wait, that's completely different!
これ、さっきやったのとちょっと違う。
This is a bit different from what we did earlier.
え、嘘でしょ！？んなことある！？
Huh, no way?! How does that even happen?!
やり直し！もうちょっとちゃんと……何で男が倒れるんだよ！
Do it over! A bit more properly... Why did the guy fall over?!
おかしおかしおかし！
That's weird, weird, weird!
ということで、じゃあもういいかな？
And with that, I guess that's enough?
え？
Huh?
じゃあもうご褒美はこんな感じでいいかなって。
So I guess this is fine as a reward.
え、だってさ、さっきやったんですよ、ちゃんと。
Eh, but we did it properly earlier.
え、じゃあ代わりますか？
Eh, then do you want to switch?
え？ちょ、ちょちょちょ。
Eh? Wait, wait, wait.
ちょ、ちょ、ちゃんと飲んで？
Wait, wait, drink it properly?
本当に！？
Really?!
なんでなんで！？
Why, why?!
飲んでほしい！寂しい！寂しいって！
I want you to drink it! I'm lonely! I'm lonely!
待って待って、どんな動きだよ！寂しい！どんな動きだよ！
Wait, wait, what kind of movement is that?! Lonely! What kind of movement is that?!
でも、この後もまだまだ続くんでしょうね？まだまだ続きます！
But it's still going to continue after this, right? It's still continuing!
この後どんな感じで続くんですか？
How is it going to continue after this?
この後は、まあね、つまづくのが補給できるから、最後まで突っ走ろうかなって、思います！
After this, well, since stumbling can be refueled, I think I'll just dash all the way to the end!
じゃあ、このままね、バリバリに進むという感じで、
So, just like this, charging forward full throttle,
頑張って！チョコ先生！頑張って！
Do your best! Choco-sensei! Do your best!
なんでお前！お前のせいで！
Why you! Because of you!
じゃあ、せっかくだから写真でも撮って応援しましょう！
Well, since we're here, let's take a photo to support her!
じゃあ、ハート作ってさ、真ん中にいちゃおうよ！あ、じゃあ行けるならね！
So, let's make a heart and get right in the middle! Ah, well, if we can!
え、本当 に！？え！？
Eh, really?! Eh?!
そんな幸せで、なんか丸くなっちゃった！
So happy, it turned into a circle!
え、ちょ、ちょ、ちゃんとくっついてください！何やっての！
Eh, wait, wait, please stick together properly! What are you doing?!
じゃ、これでね、チョコ先生が頑張れますように！チョコ先生頑張って！
Now, so that Choco-sensei can do her best! Choco-sensei, do your best!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
よし！
Alright!
じゃあ帰ろうか！いやちょっと、本当、幸せだったね。
Shall we head back? Man, that really was blissful.
何言ってるかもうわかんないから、じゃあ、帰るか。
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore, so let's head back.
じゃあ帰るね！
I'm heading back!
またね！
See you!
またね！頑張ってね！
See you! Do your best!
バイバイ！バイバイ！バイバイ！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
不思議だね いまの気持ち
It's strange, how I feel right now,
空から 降ってきたみたい
Like it came falling from the sky.
特別な季節の色が ときめを見せるよ
The special colors of the season show excitement.
初めて出会った時から
Ever since the first time we met,
予感に騒ぐ 心のMelody
My heart's melody has been buzzing with premonition.
とめられない とまらない な・ぜ
Unstoppable, won't stop, why?
届けて 切なさには
Deliver it, give a name
名前を つけようか “Snow halation”
To this bittersweetness: "Snow halation"
想いが重なるまで 待てずに
Without waiting for our feelings to overlap,
悔しいけど 好きって純情
It's frustrating, but this pure love says "I love you."
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
Hesitating in a mild fever won't do any good.
ためらってもダメだね 飛び込む勇気に賛成
Approving the courage to jump in,
まもなく Start!!
The start is near!
音もなく 気配もなく
Without sound, without a trace,
静かに運命は変わる
Fate quietly changes.
これからの未来に胸の
The heartbeat in our chest
鼓動が早くなる
Quickens for the future ahead.
例えば困ったときには
For example, when you're in trouble,
すぐに駆けつけて 抱きしめたくて
I want to rush to your side and hold you tight.
どこにいても どこでも Fly high
No matter where I am, fly high anywhere!
急いで いつの間にか
In a hurry, before I knew it,
大きくなりすぎた True emotion
It grew too big: "True emotion."
夢だけ見てるようじゃ つらいよ
It's painful to just keep dreaming.
恋人は君って言いたい
I want to say "You are my lover."
優しい目が とまどってるイヤだよ
I hate how your gentle eyes are hesitating.
このまま一気に愛情
All at once, pour my affection
あずけて Please!!
And entrust it to me, Please!!
届けて 切なさには
Let it reach you, to this pain,
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
shall we give it a name? "Snow halation"
想いが重なるまで 待てずに
Without waiting for our feelings to overlap,
悔しいけど好きって純情
it's frustrating, but this pure feeling of "I love you"
微熱の中
in the midst of a slight fever,
ためらってもダメだね
hesitating won't do any good,
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
I approve the courage to dive in—Start soon!!
お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
チョコ先生なんで我々呼んでくれたんですか？
Choco-sensei, why did you invite us?
いや今回はちょっとね、てぇてぇに挟まれたいの！
Well, this time, you see, I want to be sandwiched by tee-tee!
てぇてぇ！？ そう！
Tee-tee!? Yeah!
うちら！てぇてぇです！てぇてぇが渋滞してる！
Us! We're tee-tee! Tee-tee is causing a traffic jam!
てぇてぇがもしかしてない？お二人さん
Could it be that you two aren't actually tee-tee?
え、ぺこらちゃんって鈍感なんだから。気づいてくれてないんだから
Eh, Pekora-chan is so dense. She doesn't even notice.
いやチョコ先生マジで、あれぺこらですよ
No, Choco-sensei, seriously, that's Pekora.
え、ぺこもりてぇてぇって言われないぺこですよ
Eh, PekoMarine isn't called tee-tee, you know?
いや言われてるよ！いやいやいや、ちょっと待って
No, you are! No, no, no, wait a second.
２対１！２対１じゃん！言われてるわ！
2 against 1! It's 2 against 1! You are said to be!
言われてるの聞いたことないぺこ！
I've never heard anyone say that!
だってマリンががっつくからさ！
Because Marine comes on too strong!
え、てか、マリンがそのムーブをすればするほどね、なんかね、普段はこうやって素っ気なくしてるけど実はマリン好きぺこなんでしょ？
Eh, but you know, the more Marine does that move, the more it feels like—even though you act cold normally, you actually love Marine, right?
えが、え、えごさでもぺこまりって言ってさ
Even in ego-searching, when people say PekoMarine and then...
隣でてぇてぇって抱えること一度も見たことないぺこですよ！チョコ先生には目を覚ましていただかないと！
I've never once seen you pose together side by side calling it tee-tee! Choco-sensei, you need to wake up!
違う違う違う！こうやってね、塩対応、塩対応じゃないわ
No, no, no! Like this, salt response—wait, not salt response.
対応する時は塩対応なのよ！ペコラちゃん何なんだけどさ！
When she responds, it's a salt response! What is Pekora-chan doing?
いや、本当はね、もうちょっと可愛がって貰いたいから塩対応をしてるっていう
No, honestly, she acts cold because she wants you to dote on her a bit more, right?
ちょっと塩対応が長すぎるんだよ！
The salt response is way too long!
なんていうかチョコ先生、誕生日なんですよ！求められているものをさ、全力で提供するのが我々の仕事でしょ？
I mean, Choco-sensei, it's your birthday! Providing whatever is requested with 100% effort is our job, right?
いやそうだけどさ、じゃあチョコ先生のまじぇってペコあまりチョコてぇてぇにしないといけないってことですか？
Well, that's true, but does that mean Choco-sensei has to mix us and make it PekoMarineChoco tee-tee?
あ、交えてね！こういうこういう、こういう、交えてね
Ah, mix them! Like this, like this, mix them...
わあすごい！
Wow, amazing!
チョコ先生激てぇてぇだよ！激てぇてぇ激てぇてぇだよ！毎日渋滞だって！チョコお誕生日です！
Choco-sensei is super tee-tee! Super tee-tee, super tee-tee! It's traffic every day! It's Choco's birthday!
あ、これでいいんだ！挟まる感じ！
Ah, so this is good! Being sandwiched!
これが！これがてぇてぇペコちゃんだね！
This is! This is tee-tee Pekora, right?
ちょっと！チョコは挟まれるからチョコ！いや、ちょっと待って！
Wait! Choco gets sandwiched, so Choco—no, wait a minute!
お誕生日だからこそ許されるのよ！てぇてぇに挟まれるのは誕生日じゃなきゃ、ここに行ったらもうね、めっちゃ怒られるから！
Being sandwiched by tee-tee is only forgiven because it's your birthday! If you went there any other day, you'd get super yelled at!
どうですか？幸せですか？チョコ先生！
How is it? Are you happy, Choco-sensei?
いや、なんか、すっごいニヤニヤしてるペコらが見えましたから！
Well, I could see a grinning Pekora!
でも思っていたよりペコらが冷めてることに気づいてしまったな
But I realized Pekora is colder than I thought.
チョコ先生ともいちゃいちゃしよう！え、チョコ先生！
Let's get all cozy with Choco-sensei too! Eh, Choco-sensei!
チョコ先生とてぇてぇされたいの！？こうやってさ！交えて交えて！
You want to be tee-tee with Choco-sensei?! Like this! Mix it, mix it!
はあ、嬉しい。
Haah, I'm so happy.
ありがとう、ふたりとも。
Thank you, both of you.
いや楽しかった！
Man, that was fun!
まだまだあるんでしょ？
There's still more, right?
まだあるよ！次こそはどこに挟まりに行くのかな？
There's still more! Where are we going to get sandwiched next, I wonder?
次は最後のてぇてぇなんですからね！
Because the next one is the final tee-tee!
じゃあ次の挟まり先に行く間に、じゃあ邪魔物がなくなったペコら二人っきりにして！
Then, on our way to the next sandwich spot, leave us two alone without any nuisances!
違うの、違うの！だから、二人でチョコくま！こういくもん！
No, no! That's why, just the two of us, Chokuma! Doing this!
この後も、お楽しみに！
Look forward to what comes next too!
大胆不敵にハイカラ革命
With a bold and sudden calling, western revolution's starting
磊々落々反戦国家
Let our hearts be open to it, pacifist nation
日の丸印の二輪車転がし
Riding on a penny-farthing, sun-marked wheels roll fast
悪霊退散 ICBM
Warding off evil spirits like an ICBM
環状線を走り抜けて 東奔西走なんのその
Running through the loop line, going east and west with no fear
少年少女戦国無双
Boys and girls in a peerless Sengoku world
浮世の随に
Drifting on the fleeting floating world
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ 君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Thousand cherry blossoms lost in night, your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴 鋼の檻 其の断頭台で見下ろして
This place is a banquet in a steel cage, looking down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世之闇 嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Across three thousand worlds and eternal darkness, your lamenting song can't be heard
青藍の空 遥か彼方 その光線銃で打ち抜いて
In the deep blue sky far away, shoot through with that ray gun
百戦錬磨の見た目は将校
Battle-hardened veterans looking like officers
いったりきたりの花魁道中
Courtesans walking back and forth in procession
アイツもコイツも皆で集まれ 聖者の行進 わん つー さん し
Everyone gather around, this is the saint's march, one, two, three, four!
禅定門を潜り抜け 安楽浄土厄払い
Passing through the Zen meditation gates, driving away all misfortunes to paradise
きっと終幕は大団円 拍手の合間に
Surely the finale will be a grand denouement amidst the applause
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ 君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Thousand cherry blossoms lost in night, your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴 鋼の檻 其の断頭台で見下ろして
This place is a banquet in a steel cage, looking down from that guillotine
三千世界 常世之闇 嘆ク唄モ聞コエナイヨ
Across three thousand worlds and eternal darkness, your lamenting song can't be heard
希望の丘 遥か彼方 その閃光弾を打ち上げろ
On the hill of hope far away, launch that flashing signal flare
環状線を走り抜けて 東奔西走なんのその
Running through the loop line, going east and west with no fear
少年少女戦国無双 浮世の随に
Boys and girls in a peerless Sengoku world, drifting on the floating world
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ 君ノ声モ届カナイヨ
Thousand cherry blossoms lost in night, your voice cannot reach me anymore
此処は宴 鋼の檻 其の断頭台を飛び降りて
This place is a banquet in a steel cage, leaping down from that guillotine
千本桜 夜ニ紛レ 君が歌い僕は踊る
Thousand cherry blossoms lost in night, you sing and I dance
此処は宴 鋼の檻 さあ光線銃を撃ちまくれ
This place is a banquet in a steel cage, come on, shoot away with that ray gun!
あーい、ということで！
Alright, and with that!
ちょこ先生、誕生日おめでとう！おめでとう！
Choko-sensei, happy birthday! Happy birthday!
ねぇ、今日はあれ、てえてえに囲まれたくてうちらを呼んだとか？
Hey, did you invite us today because you wanted to be surrounded by preciousness?
あ、そうです、やっぱりね、このお二人は不滅の仲嘛、流れの絆でも絡み合って絡み合って絡み合って
Ah, that's right. After all, these two have an immortal bond, intertwining and intertwining...
深い絆で結ばれてるみたいな信頼感がめちゃめちゃ好きで
I just love that feeling of trust like being bound by a deep bond.
あ、なるほどなるほどなるほど
Ah, I see, I see, I see.
ちょっとその間に一度、人生で一度だけ入ってみたいと思って、ちょっと、しちゃいました
I thought I'd like to step into that at least once in my life, so I kinda did it.
なるほどなるほど、じゃあちょこ先生に、なんかてえてえを供給したほうがいいってことだよね？
I see, I see. So that means we should supply some preciousness to Choko-sensei, right?
え、み、見せてくれるの？
Eh, you're gonna show us?
なんかいいんだ？
Is that okay?
え、なんだろう？なんだろう？
Eh, what is it? What is it?
毛繕いでもしようか。
Shall we groom each other?
じゃあ毛繕いでもしよう、毛繕い。
Then let's groom each other, groom.
毛繕いしよう、毛繕い。
Let's groom, groom.
よしよしよしよしよしよし。
There, there, there, there...
美味しそう。おいしそうおいしそうよしよし。
Looks delicious. Delicious, delicious, there, there.
よしよし、耳だ、耳だ。
There, there, ears, ears.
ああ、でも耳も柔らかい。
Ah, but the ears are soft too.
耳は二つあるからね、もうね。
We have two ears, you know.
あいあいあいあい。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
耳も柔らかいからね。
The ears are soft, you know.
よしよしよしよし、よしよしよしよし。
There, there, there, there...
よしよしよしよし、よしよし。
There, there, there...
あ、ほらほら、ほらほら、お腹だ、お腹。
Ah, look, look, look, the tummy, tummy.
あ、お腹お腹、お腹お腹。
Ah, tummy tummy, tummy tummy.
あれなんか、あれなんか。あれ？あれ？
Wait, what, wait, what? Huh? Huh?
なんかペ ペット？ペットみたいな？
Wait, something like a pet? Like a pet?
ワルツ、ワルツじゃないですね？
Waltz? It's not a waltz, is it?
ワルツじゃないですよ？あれ？あれ？
It's not a waltz? Huh? Huh?
あれ、もしかして、うちらのことペットだと思ってますか？
Wait, do you think of us as pets?
え、もしかして、ちょ、チョコの家に住んでくれるんですか？
Eh, wait, will you come live at Choco's house?
え、そんな、そんな、そんな！
Eh, no way, no way, no way!
え、連れて行かれ、連れ去られる可能性あるこれ。
Eh, there's a chance we might get taken away.
え、ペットとして迎えられるしか。今日のゲストなんかやたらキモ耳多かった気がするな。
Eh, just being welcomed as pets... Today's guests seemed to have way too many creepy ears.
あ、そういうこと？
Ah, is that so?
そういうことか！
I see!
いやでも、チョコ、可愛いものにはちょっと、満ち足り精神で、お世話したくなっちゃって。
Well, but Choco, with cute things, kind of with a sense of fulfillment, ended up wanting to take care of them.
やばい、チョコの家のご飯美味しいよ。
Oh no, the food at Choco's house is delicious.
ねえ、ペット、あ、やべえ、やべえ。ペット、あ、でもチョコのご飯おいしい、おいしい。
Hey, pet— ah, oh no, oh no. Pet— ah, but Choco's food is delicious, delicious.
おいしいけど、お腹満たされるけど、
It's delicious, but you get full, but...
一生食うの保証されたで、チョコの朝昼晩の定食付きで。
For life, eating guaranteed, with Choco's breakfast, lunch, and dinner set meals included.
それは食べたいはまあいいけど、お風呂もちゃんと言れてあげるから！
That you'd want to eat is fine, but I'll give you nice baths too!
でもちょっと、あの、狐と狼はペットに向かないので、大丈夫です。迎えないの？
But wait, foxes and wolves aren't suited as pets, so it's fine. You're not welcoming us?
チョコ悪魔だから、そんなの、関係ないわ！
Choco is a demon, so that doesn't matter!
どうしよう、これ、逃げたほうがいいんじゃないの？これ、捕まったら、耳とか耳毛剥がされるじゃん！
What should we do? Shouldn't we run away? If we get caught like this, our ears or ear hair will get plucked!
やばいよ、やばいよ！
This is bad, this is bad!
待って、待って！逃げないで！
Wait, wait! Don't run away!
逃げられた、ちょっと、惜しいな。チョコ、ちゃんといい、複利構成用意したと思ったんだけどな。
They ran away... Oh well, that's a shame. I thought I prepared a really good benefit package.
しょうがない。
Oh well.
はい、ということで、このあとはね、ま、ここでゲストパートは終わりなのですが、まだまだ、重大発表残っているので、お楽しみに！みんなは逃げないでね！そのままで、ちゃんいい子に待っててね！またね！
Yes, so after this, well, the guest part ends here, but there are still major announcements left, so look forward to it! Don't run away everyone! Stay right there and be good kids waiting! See you later!
恋心を咲かせた純情可憐な女の子
A pure, lovely girl whose romantic feelings have blossomed
目の下クマクマ！コンシーラー
Dark circles under my eyes! Concealer!
あー！なんで今日がバレンタイン…
Ah! Why is today Valentine's Day...
ニブいあいつもちらちら、さすがに意識してるみたい
That dense guy is glancing over, looks like he's actually aware
日の浅い二人にとって
For a pair whose days together are still short
今日はそう、特別な日さ
Today is, that's right, a special day
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
スウィートな甘さを君だけに
This sweet sweetness, just for you
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want to reach your heart
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
ビターな甘さで包んでね
Wrap it in a little bitterness, okay?
ドリーミンチュチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu chu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
放課後屋上で待ち合わせ
Meeting on the rooftop after school
ドキドキ鼓動が高くなる
Heartbeats racing faster
階段上る君の足音が
The sound of your footsteps climbing the stairs
私の体を震わせた
Made my body tremble
向かい合う二人
Facing each other
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
スウィートな甘さを君だけに
This sweet sweetness, just for you
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want to reach your heart
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
ビターな甘さで包んでね
Wrap it in a little bitterness, okay?
ドリーミンチュチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu chu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
私の心と君の心
My heart and your heart
君の心と私の心
Your heart and my heart
その距離を繋ぐチョコレート
Chocolate that connects that distance
夢の中で何でも描いたこの時は
In this moment we dreamed of everything
世界に一つだけだよ
There's only one in the world
この瞬間君だけのために
This moment, just for you
スウィートなこの気持ち
These sweet feelings
贈るからね、受け入れてね
I'll give them to you, so please accept them
ドリーミンチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
スウィートな甘さを君だけに
This sweet sweetness, just for you
ドリーミンチュチュチュ、チョコレートタタタ
Dreamin' Chuchu chu, Chocolate ta-ta-ta
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコレート ta ta ta
Dreamin' Chuchu, chocolate la-ta-ta
チョコレート ta ta ta
chocolate la-ta-ta
私の心とキミの心
My heart and your heart
キミの心と私の心
Your heart and my heart
その距離を繋ぐチョコレート
Chocolate that connects that distance
夢の中で 何度も描いたこの時は
In this moment we imagined in a dream...
世界に一つだけだよ
There's only one in the whole world
この瞬間 キミだけの為に
This moment is just for you
スイートなこの気持ち
These sweet feelings of mine
送るからね 受け止めてね
Since I'll give them to you, please accept them
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコレート ta ta ta
Dreamin' Chuchu, chocolate la-ta-ta
スイートな甘さをキミだけに
This sweetness made just for you
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコレート ta ta ta
Dreamin' Chuchu, chocolate la-ta-ta
そのハートに届けたいな
I want these feelings to reach you
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコレート ta ta ta
Dreamin' Chuchu, chocolate la-ta-ta
ビターな甘さで包んでね
Cover it all up in a little bitter sweetness
ドリーみんチュチュ チョコレート ta ta ta
Dreamin' Chuchu, chocolate la-ta-ta
スイートな甘さをキミだけに
This sweetness made just for you
はーい、ということで！
So, yeah!
デスクトップとソロパートと、皆様いかがだったでしょうか？
How did you like the desktop and solo parts?
まあね、ドリーみんチュチュを歌ったということは、まあ皆様もお察しがついてるかと思うんですけど。
Well, since I sang Dreamin' Chuchu, I suppose you all have some idea.
まあ、今日はね、バレンタインデーということで、まあチョコの誕生日でもあり、
Well, today is Valentine's Day, and also Choco's birthday,
バレンタインデーということでね、チョコから愛のこもったプレゼントを皆様に告知したいと思いまーす！ということで！
and Valentine's Day, so I'd like to announce a present filled with love from Choco to everyone!
なんとなんと、今年もでーす！悠月チョコお誕生日グッズということでね、
And so, this year too! It's Yuzuki Choco's birthday merchandise,
それでは早速ご紹介していきたいと思いますー！パチパチパチー！
So let's get right into introducing them! Yay!
まずは、こちらー！
First of all, is this one!
え、玄関カーテンということでね。
Uh, an entryway curtain, you see.
いや、今回、チョコすごい迷ったの。グッズにしようかなって。今回はチョコ先生のお手伝いグッズにしましたー！
Man, Choco hesitated a lot. What kind of goods to make? This time, I made them Choco-sensei's helper goods!
そしてね、この玄関カーテン、いや、皆様ね、もうこれわかるんじゃないですか？
And this entryway curtain... hey everyone, you get it, right?
チョコ先生が「おかえり」って、お疲れ様って「おかえり、ありがと」って出迎えてくれるね。
Choco-sensei welcomes you home with "Welcome back," "Good work," "Welcome back, thank you."
いや、家に帰ったらなんと、チョコ先生が出迎えてくれます！この玄関カーテン、ぜひぜひね。
Yeah, when you get home, Choco-sensei will welcome you! Please definitely get this entryway curtain.
皆様は、まあ目隠しカーテンとしても使えるのでね、ご購入していただけたらと思います。
Since you can also use it as a blind curtain, I hope you'll purchase it.
そしてもう一つ、こちらー！ジャジャン！
And another one, here! Tada!
ちょこらコインケース！はい、こちらはね、ぜひぜひあの首から下げてね、
Chocola Coin Case! Yes, please wear this hanging from your neck,
あの、チョコ先生からお使いもらったんだ、これに入れてお使い行くんだ、つってね、
like "Choco-sensei gave me an errand, I'll put it in here and go on an errand," and
ぜひぜひ使ってください。
please definitely use it.
そしてね、こちらのトートバッグ！いや、お使いのものをね、ぜひぜひ入れてね、
And this tote bag! Put your errand items in here and
皆様お持ち帰ってください。
everyone please take them home.
そしてそして、今回も出ます！耳かきASMRボイス！
And this time too! Ear-cleaning ASMR voice!
ということでね、はい、1つ目のボイスが、寝落ちのお使いボイスということで、はい、寝落ちのね、甘々チョコ先生が甘えながらお使いを頼んでくるボイスです。
Yes, the first voice is the falling-asleep errand voice, a sweet Choco-sensei asking you to run errands while acting spoiled.
そして2つ目がよく寝っ転がりボイスということで、いや、こちらはね、あの帰ってきて、チョコ先生が「お疲れ、ありがと」って迎えてくれる甘々ボイスです！ご褒美もあるのでお楽しみに！
And the second is the cozy nap voice! She welcomes you back with "Good work, thanks," super sweet! There are rewards too, look forward to it!
そしてね、こちら、なんと！フルセットご購入の方のみ、悠月チョコ直筆サイン＆箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード！
And this, what! Only for those who purchase the full set, a postcard with Yuzuki Choco's handwritten signature & hot-stamped message!
えー、悠月チョコ直筆サイン＆箔押しメッセージ入り、なんと！Nardack先生描き下ろしのこのイラストのポストカードがついてきまーす！ちゃんと1枚1枚チョコね、あのサイン書くのでね、ぜひぜひ皆様は大切に保管してくださいね。
Uh, Yuzuki Choco's handwritten signature & message, a postcard with this illustration drawn by Nardack-sensei! Choco will sign each one by one, so please keep them safe.
はい、そして特典ボイス！チョコ先生とお使いーツアー！ということでね、こちらはシチュエーションボイスとなっておりますのですが、なんとね、なんとチョコ先生とツーアで、お使いを頼んでくるっていうね、しかもツーアつないだりしながらお買い物ができ るっていうボイスとなっておりますので、ぜひぜひ皆様お楽しみに！
And bonus voice! Choco-sensei and Errand Tour! A situation voice where Choco-sensei asks you to run errands on tour, shopping while connected on a call!
グッズのことかはこの辺にしといて
Let's leave the merchandise talk for around here,
このあとは もう一つチョコからのお知らせがあるのですが
After this, I have one more announcement from Choco, but
まずは こちら お知らせに行くには
first, to get to this announcement,
毎年恒例のレッドカーペットレッドカーペッーと！
as per our annual tradition, the red carpet! Yes, the red carpet!
それでは皆様、チョコにいつものように綺麗なね 赤いレッドカーペットを引いて、準備を作ってください、よろしくお願いします！
So everyone, please lay out a nice red carpet for Choco like always and get ready! Thank you so much!
それでは レッドカーペット スタート！
Now then, red carpet, start!
はい、このレッドカーペットはね、まあ毎年恒例と言いますか、チョコの誕生日にね、欠かせないものとなっております。
Yes, this red carpet, well, you could say it's an annual tradition, is an indispensable part of Choco's birthday.
ハイ皆様からね、そう、その「おめでとう」おめでとうってね、おめでとうって慣れてくれたものが、ちゃんとチョコに道を作ってくれるのです！
Yes, and everyone saying "Congratulations, congratulations", getting used to saying "Congratulations", creates a path right for Choco!
はい、このあとのね、みんなに用意したプレゼントに続く道なので、ぜひぜひ参加していただけたら嬉しいです。
Yes, since this is the path leading to the presents prepared for everyone afterwards, I'd be so happy if you could join in.
あ、それと、さっき言い忘れちゃったんだけど、あの今回のねグッズなんと21時5分からカートがオープンするので、最後までゆっくり安心して見ててください。
Oh, and I forgot to mention earlier, but as for this merchandise, the cart will actually open at 21:05, so please watch relaxedly and securely until the end.
そしてね今回チョコ、なんと初めてねこの配信のあとにメン限ライブもね、あのちょっと、ちょっと考えちゃってるんで、よかったらね21時15分からこのあとメン限ライブもあるので、ぜひぜひ皆様まだねメンバー登録してないよって方はねこの機会にメンバー登録よろしくお願いします！
And also, this time, Choco, amazingly for the first time, is thinking about doing a membership-only live stream right after this broadcast, so if you'd like, since there's a membership-only live stream starting at 21:15, everyone who hasn't registered as a member yet, please take this opportunity to sign up!
そしてそしてなんとね皆様このステージ、え、なんかいつもと違いませんか？なんか若っぽくないですか？
And and, everyone, this stage—eh, doesn't it look a bit different from usual? Doesn't it look a bit youthful?
そう今回運営さんにお願いしてなんとなんとチョコのねお誕生日ステージ装飾お願いして、こちらって見せたいんだけど、こっちのほうが綺麗に見えるから、
That's right, this time I asked management, and they decorated Choco's birthday stage, and I wanted to show you "over here", but it looks prettier this way...
その、たまっちゃった、繋げてもらいたいなってって、
Um, I got stuck, I wanted you to connect it...
やった！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
あ、あとちょっと、あともうちょっと、あとまっちゃんた、あともうちょっと、
Ah, just a little more, just a little more...
行くよ？せーの、えい！
Ready? Here we go, ei!
ありがとう！ここから！ありがとう！
Thank you! From here! Thank you!
それじゃあステージ見てもらおうかな？
Now then, shall I have you look at the stage?
あー、みんな見えてる？これ！さっき言ってた運営さんに作ってもらったステージ見えてるみんな？めちゃめちゃすごくないですか？
Ah, can everyone see this? The stage management made for us that I mentioned earlier, can everyone see it? Isn't it super amazing?
そう、今回は悪魔をちょっとイメージしてお願いしてみました！まあチョコ悪魔なんでね、若いイメージだから。
That's right, this time I asked them to make it with a bit of a devil image! Well, since Choco is a devil, you know, with a youthful image.
ということで、皆様レッドカーペットもありがとうございます、繋げていただいて！
So everyone, thank you for the red carpet as well, for connecting it!
そしてそして、まあ問題もしてたね、チョコからのプレゼントということで、何とこれから発表したいと思います！
And and, as for the gift from Choco that we were wondering about, I'd like to announce it now!
それでは聴いてください、新曲「Sickbay Mistake」。
Now then, please listen, the new song "Sickbay Mistake".
静かな午後 淡い日差し
Quiet afternoon, faint sunlight
カーテンが揺れる キミの声
Curtains sway, your voice
近づく足音だけで分かる
I know just by your approaching footsteps
さあ 今日はどんな味がホ・シ・イ
Now, what kind of taste do you want today?
騒ぐ悪魔の誘惑 What do you want?
A buzzing devil's temptation, what do you want?
Ah.. Sickbayで待ち合わせ Mistakeなヨカン
Ah... Meeting at Sickbay, a feeling of a mistake.
扉開けてさあこっちへおいで
Open the door and come over here.
教科書に載っていないこの気持ちは何ですか?
What is this feeling not written in textbooks?
可愛い 可愛い 顔みせて
Show me your cute, cute face.
Sickbayで会いましょう Mistakeしちゃう?
Let's meet at Sickbay, will it be a mistake?
永遠に続く時間よ止まって
Time that goes on forever, stop.
教室じゃみせられない笑顔の秘密は
The secret of the smile you can't show in the classroom
甘い 甘い お菓子あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet candy.
囁く 悪魔の誘惑 いかが?
How about a whispering devil's temptation?
秒針のリズム追い越してく
Overtaking the rhythm of the second hand,
聴かせて もっとキミの鼓動
let me hear your heartbeat even more.
触れる視線で身体中
All over my body with touching gazes,
騒ぐの もうどうしようもないくらい
it's buzzing to the point of no return.
禁断の果実 甘い もう後に戻れない
Forbidden fruit, sweet; I can't turn back now.
目が合って はにかんで 触れ合って 見つめ合って
Eyes meeting, shyly smiling, touching, gazing at each other,
永遠の楽園に誘う愛の言葉を 耳元で囁いて あげる
whispering words of love in your ear, inviting you to an eternal paradise.
Sickbayで待ってるわ Mistakeな時間
Waiting at Sickbay, a mistaken time.
扉閉めて もっと近づいて
Close the door and get closer.
神様も止められないこの気持ちの正体を
The true nature of this feeling that even God can't stop,
知らないふりは もう出来ない
I can't pretend not to know anymore.
Sickbayで会いたいのか Mistakeしましょう
Wanting to meet at Sickbay, let's make a mistake.
永遠はここにあるって信じて
Believing that eternity is right here.
キミにしかみせられない笑顔の裏側は
The backside of the smile I can only show you
甘い 甘い 果実あげる
I'll give you sweet, sweet fruit.
囁く 悪魔の誘惑 もっといかが?
How about even more of the whispering devil's temptation?
いつでもここでまってる My Cute student♡
Waiting here anytime, My Cute student♡
みんな 最後まで見てくれてありがとう！このあとはメン限ライブもあるのでお楽しみにー！
Everyone, thank you for watching till the end! There's a member-only stream after this, so please look forward to it!